Iván Urra Full Stack Developer

I am a Full Stack Web Developer. I like to solve problems and I am excited about the possibilities that technology offers to help people. I value commitment, hard work, and motivation to learn something new every day. I love teamwork and helping others. I have worked for more than ten years in highly regulated IT environments.

Technologies & Methodologies

JavaScript MongoDB

React JS Git & GitHub

Next JS UX/UI Design

Gatsby JS Figma

HTML & (S)CSS Agile

Node JS SCRUM

Express JS ITIL

Education

2020

Full Stack Web Development Graduate

Ironhack

Learned Frontend and Backend technologies.

2002 - 2006

Bachelor's degree, Tourism

University Carlos III of Madrid

2000 - 2002

FP Higher Degree: Application Development

I.E.S. Ciudad Escolar

Languages

Spanish: Native English: B2

Contact

https://ivanurra.dev

ivan.urra.dev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ivanurra github.com/ivanurra

Projects

Portfolio

ivanurra.dev

→ My portfolio website. Built with React and Next.

Cinemabox

cinemabox.netlify.app

♣ App about movies and TV shows. Built with MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS & NodeJS (MERN App).

Cocktail Guide

cocktailguide.herokuapp.com

♣ App about cocktails. Built with MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Handlebars & Axios. Data from an external API.

El Politico

ivanurra.github.io/elPolitico-videogame

★ Web browser videogame. Deployed from scratch in five days by using JavaScript, Canvas, HTML & CSS.

Relevant Experience

AUG 2021 - PRESENT

REMOTE

Full Stack Web Developer

@ Secuoyas

- Write modern, performant, maintainable code for a diverse array of client.
- Work with a variety of different languages and frameworks such as JavaScript, React, Gatsby and Next.
- ◆ Communicate and collaborate with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, and stakeholders on a daily basis.

MAR 2021 - AUG 2021

MADRID

Full Stack Web Developer

@ Auro Group

- → Built and shipped the new Auro website (frontend).
- Worked closely with designer and commercial team to develop the website using JavaScript, Vue, Nuxt and Vuetify.
- ◆ Developed and maintained code for in-house projects